http://www.coombecastle.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Coombe Castle is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy.
We've structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit Coombe Castle, on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Coombe Castle.
Coombe Castle, provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our Privacy Statement, practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
We will only collect sufficient information on you to allow us to communicate with you in an appropriate way. This information will include your name and contact details as appropriate. In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience and more detailed contact preferences.
Coombe Castle uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, and to personalise our web site for you.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact.
Coombe Castle will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other closely related entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above.
Coombe Castle will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first requesting your permission. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honour such requests.
Links to third party web sites on the site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Coombe Castle site. Coombe Castle has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their Privacy Statement. Thus, Coombe Castle does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do so at your own risk.
Coombe Castle is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Email enquiries are transmitted by insecure means and stored off-line.
Coombe Castle International,
The Creamery, Western Way,
Melksham, Wiltshire SN12 8FH, UK
Contact Us · Privacy Policy · Terms & Conditions
Copyright © 2020 Coombe Castle International Ltd
Coombe Castle International
HomeOur Products
Coombe Castle Cheeses
Blue Cheese
Blue StiltonShropshire Blue Back
Cheddar Cheese
Dorset DrumExtra Mature CheddarMature CheddarMild Cheddar Back
Sweet Blends
Chocolate and OrangeCreamy CinnamonRaspberry TippleSticky ToffeeWensleydale with ApricotsWensleydale with BlueberriesWensleydale with CherriesWensleydale with CranberriesWensleydale with LemonWensleydale with Mango and GingerWensleydale with Mango and PapayaWensleydale with Pear and Apple Back
Savoury Blends
Cheddar and ClaretCrackingtonDouble Gloucester with Blue StiltonDouble Gloucester with Chives and OnionFiddlers GreenFiery SpiceGaelic GoldJalapeno SpiceMarrakechMoroccan SpiceOlive GrovePickwickRed LionSaxonshires Back
Regionals
CaerphillyCheshireDouble GloucesterLancashireRed LeicesterSage DerbyWensleydale Back
Back
Devon Cream Company
Double CreamClotted CreamClotted Cream with BrandyCreme FraicheSoured CreamButter Back
Partner Brands
Cheese
Barber’sBelton FarmCahill’sCollier’sCornish Cheese CompanyDelamereDragonFord FarmGuinness® CheddarHartington CreameryIlchester®Mull of KintyreWensleydaleWexford Back
Butter
Collier’s Welsh ButterDragon ButterDelamere Goats ButterDelamere Spreadable Goats ButterSt Helen’s Goats Butter Back
